greedge.com 2012-09-19

# GREedge.com

GREedge.com has created this privacy statement ("Statement") in order to demonstrate our commitment to customer privacy. Privacy on the GREedge.com web site (the "Site") is of great importance to us. Because we gather important information from our visitors and customers, we have established this Statement as a means to communicate our information gathering and dissemination practices. We reserve the right to change this Statement at any time, so please visit GREedge.com regularly to review our privacy statement.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should contact GREedge.com by emailing [info@greedge.com](mailto:info@greedge.com) , or by calling +91 98844 53276

**Collected Information**

We require customers who register to use the services offered on our Site (collectively, the "Services") to give us contact information, such as their name, address, phone number, and e-mail address, and billing information, such as billing name and address, credit card number, Examination Dates, Mobile Number and model etc. to use the service. We also receive and may store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many Web sites, we use "cookies" and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses [www.greedge.com](http://www.greedge.com/). More information on our use of "cookies" can be found below.

GREedge.com uses the information that we collect to set up the Services for our customers. We may also use the information to contact customers to further discuss customer interest in our company, the Adaptive Learning Service that we provide, and to send information regarding our company or partners, such as promotions and events. Customer email addresses and any personal customer information will not be distributed or shared with third parties. Customers can opt out of being contacted by us, or receiving such information from us, at any time by sending an email to [info@greedge.com](mailto:info@greedge.com). We may also email information regarding updates to the Adaptive Learning Service or company, and will send a Student Newsletter.

In order to tailor our subsequent communications to you and continuously improve our products and services (including registration), we may also ask you to provide us with information regarding your personal or professional interests, experience with our products and services, and more detailed contact preferences. Customers and visitors always have the option of choosing not to provide us with this information.

Except as we explicitly state at the time we request information, we do not disclose to third parties the information provided. All financial and billing information that we collect through the Site is used solely to check the qualifications of prospective customers and to bill for the Adaptive Learning Service. This billing information is not used by GREedge.com for marketing or promotional purposes. GREedge.com uses a third-party intermediary to manage the credit card processing. This intermediary uses the information for the sole purpose of credit card processing.

GREedge.com may also collect certain information from visitors to and customers of the Site, such as Internet addresses. This information is logged to help diagnose technical problems, and to administer our Site in order to constantly improve the quality of the Adaptive Learning Service. We may also track and analyze non-identifying and aggregate usage and volume statistical information from our visitors and customers and provide such information to third parties.

**Special Relationships**

GREedge.com has a number of relationships with business partners with whom we may share your personal information for the purpose of providing a service, fulfilling an order or completing a transaction. For example, we use certain vendors for the purpose of providing credit card transaction and check processing services. These vendors verify your purchase information, such as credit card number or checking account number, and authorize your transaction. In doing so, they have access to data about users, but they are prohibited from using this information for any other purpose. We also strongly urge you to read the privacy policy of our business partner at the business partners site.

**Cookies**

GREedge.com uses software tags called "cookies" to identify customers when they visit our site. Cookies are used to remember user preferences and maximize performance of our services. The information we collect with cookies is not sold, rented, or shared with any outside parties. Users who disable their Web browser's ability to accept cookies will be able to browse our Website but will not be able to successfully use our Adaptive Learning Service.

We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser's "help" file. Persistent cookies enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site.

This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by GREedge.com only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

*Third Party Cookies:* We may from time to time engage third parties to track and analyze non-personally identifiable usage and volume statistical information from visitors to our website to help us administer our website and improve its quality. Such third parties may use cookies to help track visitor behavior. Such cookies will not be used to associate individual website visitors to any personally identifiable information. All data collected by such third parties on behalf of GREedge.com is used only to provide us with information on site usage and is not shared with any other third parties.

**Web Beacons**

Web pages may contain an electronic file called a web beacon, that allows a web site to count users who have visited that page or to access certain cookies. GREedge.com uses web beacons in the following ways:

**Within the GREedge.com web sites**

  * GREedge.com uses web beacons within the GREedge.com web sites in order to count users and to recognize users by accessing GREedge.com cookies.
  * Being able to access GREedge.com cookies allows us to personalize your experience when you visit GREedge.com web sites that are located both on and off of the GREedge.com domain.

**HTML email**

GREedge.com's practice is to include web beacons in HTML-formatted email messages (messages that include graphics) that GREedge.com, or its agents, sends in order to determine which email messages were opened and to note whether a message was acted upon.

In general, any file served as part of a web page, including an ad banner, can act as a web beacon. GREedge.com may also include web beacons from other companies within pages served by GREedge.com so that GREedge.com's advertisers may receive auditing, and reporting.

**Log Files**

GREedge.com maintains log files of the traffic that visits our site. We do not link any information gathered in these log files to personally identifying information. Log files are used to manage traffic loads and information technology requirements for providing reliable service. Information collected includes IP addresses and browser types.

**Tracking of Usage Statistics**

In order to effectively deliver personalized and adaptive learning experiences, we gather information about your learning and reading patterns including but not limited to your interactions with the toolbar, our other learning software and your own web browsing patterns. You agree that this process is essential for proper functioning of the Toolbar and other software provided by GREedge.com licensors. If, for any reason, you do not wish such data to be collected or stored, please discontinue use of this toolbar or other GREedge.com software with immediate effect.

**Information Security**

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

All information gathered on the site is stored and maintained in secure facilities that limit access to authorized personnel only.

**Retention of Information**

GREedge.com will keep personal information of its users for as long as they are registered subscribers or users of our products and services, and for a reasonable time thereafter

**Legal Disclaimer**

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.

  12. RESOLUTION OF DISPUTES.  
If a dispute arises between you and GREedge.com, our goal is to provide you with a neutral and cost effective means of resolving the dispute quickly. Accordingly, you and GREedge.com agree that we will resolve any claim or controversy at law or equity that arises out of this Toolbar License or our services (a "Claim") in accordance with one of the paragraphs below or as we and you otherwise agree in writing. Before resorting to these alternatives, we strongly encourage you to first contact us directly to seek a resolution by sending email to [info@greedge.com](mailto:info@greedge.com). We will consider reasonable requests to resolve the dispute through alternative dispute resolution procedures, such as mediation or arbitration, as alternatives to litigation.
  13. Force Majeure  
The GREedge.com licensor shall not be directly responsible for break or disruption of service or availability on account of Force Majeure circumstances, making it impossible to render the service to the subscriber. However, the subscriber shall continue to pay all and any charges as per the terms of the agreement notwithstanding the force majeure conditions.
  14. Arbitration  
Any dispute or claims arising between the parties hereto shall be referred to arbitration by an arbitrator to be appointed by the GREedge.com licensors. The arbitration shall be held at Chennai, India and the same shall be governed by the provisions of the Arbitration and Conciliation act, 1996 and amendments thereto.
  15. Jurisdiction  
Any dispute shall be subject to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts in Chennai, India only.

MISCELLANEOUS PROVISIONS. If for any reason a court of competent jurisdiction finds any provision or portion of this Toolbar License to be unenforceable, the remainder of the Toolbar License will continue in full force and effect. Sections 2-7, 10, 12, and 13 of this Toolbar License will survive any termination of this Toolbar License. This Toolbar License constitutes the entire agreement between the parties with respect to the subject matter hereof and supersede and replace all prior or contemporaneous understandings or agreements, written or oral, regarding such subject matter. To the extent that there is a conflict between the terms of this Toolbar License and the terms of the GREedge.com Privacy Policy or GREedge.com Terms of Service, this Toolbar License shall have precedence as to the subject matter of this Toolbar License. Except as otherwise provided in Section 9, any modifications of this Toolbar License must be in writing and agreed to by both parties. Any waiver of any provision of these Toolbar License will be effective only if in writing and signed by GREedge.com.

**Questions Or Additional Information.** If you have questions regarding this Toolbar License, or wish to obtain additional information, please send an e-mail to [info@greedge.com](mailto:info@greedge.com).
